# Kelebogile Mokwena

Address: E1112 Masosobane Section, Phokeng, Rustenburg, North West

**Phone:** +27 (0) 78 685 6323 / +27 (0) 67 835 2057

Email: mokwenakw@gmail.com

### **OBJECTIVE**

Junior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2017 to 10/2018

## IT Technician Assistant (Internship)- Bonalesedi Nursing College, Krugersdorp, Gauteng Department of Health

- Installed Software, modified and repaired hardware and resolved technical issues.
- Provides base level IT support to non-technical personnel within the college
- Create a script to uninstall Old AV that needs a password to manually uninstall.
- Set up PC and desktop for new staff members
- Upgrading of existing systems.

Reason for leaving: Contract Ended

10/2016 - 10/2017

# Money Market Clerk - Shoprite Checkers, Brits, North West

- Bookings of flights, bus and live events tickets.
- Account payments, Money transfer and Telephonic inquiries.
- Lotto payments and payouts

Reason for leaving: Found an internship related to what I studied

12/2013 - 09/2016

## Front end Cashier - Shoprite Checkers, Brits, North West

 Greet customers as they arrive in the store and provide them with information regarding products and/or service. Respond to customers' complaints and take necessary actions to resolve their issues. Take payment in exchange of items sold. Bag, box and wrap purchased items. Identify prices of goods using scanner. Enter transactions in the cash register and provide customer with the total bill. Sort and count currency and coins. Issue receipts and change to customers. Count money at the beginning and ending of each shift. Process credit card payments. Assist in stocking shelves, rotating merchandise and marking prices. Keep the work area tidy and clean.

### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2020

Diploma in Information Technology,

University of South Africa

2010 - 2011

**NCV L4 Information Technology and Computer Sciences**, ORBIT FET College

2012

IT Essentials: PC Hardware and Software, ORBIT FET College

2008

Matric Certificate, Bafokeng High School

#### **SKILLS**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- CB drivers Licence
- Database: Microsoft Office Access
- Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, Access
- Operating system:
  Microsoft Windows
  7, 8, 10 and Linux
- Programming: HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL

### **LANGUAGES**

Speak, Read and Write Setswana, English, Zulu, Xhosa

## **REFERENCES**

Name Keneilwe Morabe

Position Stock Administrator Manager at Shoprite

Po Ce Na Po	osition ell ame osition ell	060 417 8066 Refiwe Motau	nalesedi Nursing College er at Shoprite Checkers	